To be continued...
Is this really the best you can do?
I have to say I'm unimpressed.
You can call forth an angel and command flame.
Surely you can be below me, can't you?
Oh, well, guess not!
Why don't you keep your mouth shut?
You're a lot cuter when you're not talking!
Well, I happen to think you would be a lot cuter with your pretty little head mounted on my wall!
It must really suck to be you right now, frozen in time and completely surrounded.
Oh, well, bye-bye, flame girl.
A point-blank shot to the noggin.
That'll sure dampen your spirit, eh?
It really is too bad.
I was actually starting to enjoy her.
And now she's dead.
Now that that's settled, you're on deck, Shido.
Let's have a little fun.
Monologuing always gets the bad guy in trouble.
Not part of your plan?
If you'd rather tuck your tail between your legs and run home to mommy, I'd completely understand.
Ha!
Not in your wildest dreams, flame girl!
Ah!
Olive!
What are you doing?
I've heard of pieces!
Come on!
Damn you!
Comes up kill!
Don't lie to all!
Oh, come on!
Don't give up on me already!
You can't quit just when your opponent is warmed up!
It's bad form!
I promise you this.
You'll be sorry you ever decided to mess with me!
Soft kill!
Yeah, show me what you got!
What's happening?
Coterie!
It looks like your devil's luck has run out!
Are you alright?
Kamal!
Make it all!
Rally to me immediately!
Turn them on to ashes!
Do it, Kamal!
Pick up your weapon!
This fight's not over yet, and the war's not over yet either!
Well, come on then!
Let's have some more of that destruction you love so much!
This is the fight you wanted!
This is the war you wanted, isn't it?
If you can't face the muzzle of a gun anymore, it's over.
Time for you to die!
Coterie!
If you keep pushing like this, she will die!
Isn't the point of Rattasker to resolve conflicts without killing spirits?
You have to stop!
Stay back!
No!
Don't!
Please!
Big Brother, look out!
Big Brother!
Brunt!
It will be he virus!
Would you like me to operate?
Yes, please.
Thank you, Doctor.
Alrighty then!
Nurse, please hand me my scalpel!
Scalpel
You're fine
Toka she's here, too
Why am I in a sick bay well you're awake that's good
Like the anesthesia didn't work good thing you woke up before I cut you open
I really am sorry. I hope I didn't scare you, please. I'm fine really
Hey, reina tell me what am I doing in here the thing is you were knocked out in the battle with kurumi
So we brought you here just to be on the safe side. Yeah, yeah, that's right
But I don't know what happened after that. What about toka. She's just sleeping isn't she no hey
Where is kotari? What was that power you need to calm down shin?
No, I'm not gonna calm down wait. What about kurumi and mana? Is she all right and everyone from school?
Everything will be just fine. Do you feel better now?
Yeah
Everybody is doing okay, and no one was killed all things considered it could have been much worse
As far as origami and mana
They were both taken by members of the AST
We can't be certain yet, but our best guess is they were brought to tengu hospital
Kurumi ran off while she had the chance and as you can see toka is sleeping
Even though she's hurt she wanted to be by your side toka cares more about you than she does her own recovery
Not to worry though. She's gonna be fine
That's good, but this isn't the end is it of course not kotari can I see her
She can't hear or see us through the protective wall you're going to be on your own in there
Hey you I didn't expect to see you up and about how are you feeling better I guess
What about you are you feeling okay?
I feel like my normal super cute self. I'm not sure it's normal to call yourself cute. You don't think I'm cute
No, you're right. I guess you're kind of cute
But kotari tell me the truth. Are you really your spirit?
You
Answer me are you a spirit or not?
Well, if I told you that I wasn't a spirit would you believe me of course if you said so that I would
Is that right you believe what someone says even when you've seen the contrary to be true
If you want my two cents that seems like a fast way to make a fool of yourself
If I can't even trust my little sis what kind of brother would that make me?
Look I said I'd believe you I always will no matter what
I think I'm a human being I mean, I wouldn't call myself a spirit
Although the observation equipment might beg to differ
I have no doubt the machine says I'm lying to you
Wait, what do you mean?
I was born into the Itsuka family
And that much I know for sure
But five years ago somehow I became a flame spirit
That might not be the best way to put it
I guess it's more accurate to say I became a person who possesses spirit powers
Seriously?
This might sound nuts, but I knew about this
That's impossible. I never said anything to you
No, no, that's not what I'm saying
I had this dream
Kotari, no
Big brother, big brother, no
I have to say I'm not sure I agree with the part where I was screaming out for you and crying like a big baby
But more or less that's the way I remember it, too
It's possible it may have flowed to you through the path when the spirit powers returned to me
I see
But I still don't get it. What happened?
How did you become a spirit?
I wish I could tell you, but the truth is I don't remember
Huh?
I mean obviously I know something must have happened back then
But for the life of me, I don't know what
I remember becoming a spirit
but I don't know how
I don't know how
or even why for that matter
How can you become a spirit?
I wish I could tell you, but the truth is I don't remember
Huh?
I mean obviously I know something must have happened back then
But for the life of me, I don't know what
I remember becoming a spirit, but I don't know how
know how or even why for that matter how can you forget something so important look who's talking
you're in no position to pass judgment on the forgetful front big bro but then again you're
right it's kind of weird that neither of us has any memory of it all you'd think we would remember
everything who knows maybe somebody erased our memories for some reason well it's a theory
anyway after that i was discovered by ratatasker then i found out the truth about what was going
on behind the scenes and i decided i wanted to save the spirits but once you got past that big fire
you lived a pretty typical life how are you able to blend in with the regular kids what you don't
remember that part either i was able to be a normal girl because you sealed away my spirit powers really
wait are you serious yeah didn't i tell you yesterday don't let me forget to give this back
to you shido i don't fully understand why but for some inexplicable reason you're able to seal away
a spirit's power and that's why you were chosen by ratatasker to talk to the spirits you're special
shido so my regeneration ability came from uh yes your ability came from mine now listen up come
over here and stand right in front of me why should i do that because i said so fine
i told you to be careful didn't i but you didn't listen to me if i hadn't come to my senses you'd be
dead meat you're very lucky what the heck were you thinking anyway you idiot running out in front of my
light in a fire like that you scared me i thought you'd lost it and i was right you weren't yourself
yeah when the spirit powers returned to me i lost control all i wanted to do was break something or
better yet kill someone if i got the chance i was scared it was like i was a different person
who knows what other awful things i've done that i have no memory of
there's no telling if it's that easy for me to lose control over myself i wouldn't be shocked if
i already have killed stop talking like that just ignore me i don't even know what i'm talking about
but i do think i know why i snapped out of it yesterday it's because you stepped in front of me
thanks for saving the day big bro about your spirit power will it come back to me
i don't really know unfortunately spirit stuff isn't always easy to understand all i know for
sure is this you'll have to seal it just like you did before but to seal it away i'd have to
yes take me on a date and make me fall in love the same way you did with toka and yoshino you have to
hey kautari are you all right can you stand yeah i'm okay you don't need to worry about me please
talk to me
shin that's enough for today all right you go ahead i'll handle things from here no i can't
we'll have lots to discuss later but for now go on okay
shino i've been looking everywhere i was worried because when i woke up you were gone
but you're awake so does this mean you're feeling better i don't know do you mind if we talk later
yeah okay
i give her two days i doubt she'll last much longer than that eventually her spirit power
will be too much for her to handle what do you mean by that once the power overtakes her completely
kotari will no longer be anything like the little sister you once knew and loved in just under 48 hours
we'll have you go on a date with her that'll be your best chance to make sure she doesn't slip away
forever sorry sir but you're not allowed to see her not even her family can do that yet i do
apologize but i'm afraid i don't know when she's going to be allowed visitors but why is it really that
bad i wish i could help but unfortunately at this time i can't discuss her condition with you ma'am please
shito origami
i'm glad you're safe is toka okay uh yeah she's uh she's good
never mind
so you came here to see mana huh yeah well i tried to but the nurse wouldn't allow it
what i can't go into specifics but for mana's recovery they're using some highly classified
equipment on her so until she's moved to the general ward there's no way they'll let anyone see
her and if you try to force your way in it won't end well i know that's why you're here
huh to see mana and nobody else oh well obviously i came to visit you too uh-huh
yeah i'd better get a move on i'm sure you're really busy i bet you have lots of doctor's
appointments and stuff like that later
oragami are you all right i can't make it back to my room on my own will you please carry me
i should get a nurse carry me right now come on who needs a nurse can you walk no i can't what you need
is a wheelchair i'll get one no please stop i can't handle that i'll vomit from motion sickness
what do you expect me to do about it take it back me huh you heard me right
hey origami don't you think you're holding on a little tight there um no
you're in room 305 all the way in the west wing aren't you okay that tickles please don't man up
uh origami stop
oh boy all right that's enough hey licking is crossing the line okay
well then i'm just gonna go ahead and go peel it uh well i suppose i can make that happen
now feed it to me don't you think this is getting a little crazy
you want to see crazy try not feeding me
now put it in my
oh please stop wait don't stop no do it's gross and awesome too oh god too much
great i'm glad to hear you liked it so anyway i'm gonna take off now but what about my temperature
i'm gonna need your help sticking it in my mouth oh all right fine why am i sitting down to take your
temperature this is inappropriate what the heck is going on well you seem to get excited by kuromi's
behavior since you like that sort of thing i thought i'd turn up the volume and get more aggressive
here are the rules big boy if you look you have to touch
goodbye origami i'm really leaving this time can i ask you one more thing
hmm it's important i want you to tell me what happened after the fight with kurumi tokisaki yesterday
because i thought i saw another spirit floating in the sky she was surrounded by flames flames she
could control then i must have passed out the next thing i knew i woke up in here so i want you to
tell me what i missed no matter how insignificant the details i want to know everything that happened
and everything you know about this flame spirit oh well uh i got knocked out too so i don't know much
why do you ask just curious well do you know her the flame spirit i mean yes i do five years ago
there was a massive fire in tengu city it mainly broke out in a small neighborhood called nanko
and that's when i first saw her the day she burned my parents alive big brother
ever since she killed my family i've spent every waking moment searching for her
no one should ever have to feel the way i felt that day she's the reason i joined the ast
the reason i trained as hard as i could she's why i get out of bed in the morning and she's what i
think about when i go to sleep i promised myself back then that when i had the chance i wouldn't
hesitate i'd wrap my hands around her throat look her in the eyes and crush every last bit of
remaining life and now my opportunity is right in front of me this is the moment i've been waiting
for i swear to you i will kill the flame spirit
i haven't been waiting for the 모elle on something so much
you've been waiting for the brightness of it
oh that if you want something in the aftermath of this video
i can score not enough time
i Webb had a few times
我不太好感度の波に振り回されて
遊ばれてる オモチャモチャ それいか
It's long way
果てしなすぎる 君への道のりを
転得力で走り続けるよ
Will you meet me again? Will you believe me again?
Will you be looking for love?
Take the world!
The world will end before the end of the world
If you are laughing, you'll be happy
Lady Linder
рыch